{
    "question": "10. What is the message of the song above?    a. Counting the number\r\nc. Have fun together\r\nb. Friendship\r\nd. Sailing\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>c have fun together semoga bermanfaat ya</p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a. Counting the number</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "usually-a-wears-tigor-on-a-scarf-windy-day-arrange-the-jumbled-wo-835",
            "question": "Usually-a-wears-tigor-on-a scarf-windy day\r\n Arrange the jumbled words to the correct sentences!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Usually Tigor wears a scarf on a windy day </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>sorry if I&#039;m wrong :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "26-ati-karep-bandha-cupet-ukara-kasebut-kalebu-purwakanthi-983",
            "question": "26. Ati karep bandha cupet.    Ukara kasebut kalebu purwakanthi ....\r\nA. Purwakanthi guru swara\r\nB Purwakanthi guru sastra\r\nC. Purwakanthi lumaksita\r\nD. Purwakanthi guru wilangan\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B. Purwakanti  guru  sasta</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "3-ms-gina-have-you-taken-your-lunch-sandy-ms-gina-well-l-857",
            "question": "3. Ms. Gina : Have you taken your lunch?\r\nSandy\r\nMs. Gina : Well, let's go find some meals.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>3. Ms. Gina : Have you taken your lunch?\n</p><p>Sandy: <strong>No, I have not.</strong>\n</p><p>Ms. Gina : Well, let&#039;s go find some meals.\u200b</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Pertanyaan dari Ms.Gina menggunakan bentuk Present Perfect Tense karena dia bertanya apakah Sandy sudah makan atau belum. Maka jawaban sesuai dengan kalimat yang dicetak tebal, yaitu memberitahukan bahwa Sandy belum makan, karenanya, Ms.Gina mengajak Sandy untuk mencari makanan bersama.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-pilihan-ganda-neither-nor-457",
            "question": "Contoh soal pilihan ganda neither nor",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>contoh soal pilihan ganda neither nor</p><p>1. Neither Budi .......... Badu came to the party last night.</p><p>a. or</p><p>b. nor</p><p>c. and</p><p>d. but</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Kalimat di atas merupakan contoh soal pilihan ganda dari neither nor yang jawabannya adalah poin b. nor.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "change-these-sentences-into-simple-past-tense-baseed-on-the-give-685",
            "question": "Change these sentences into simple past tense, baseed on the given Marka in bracket! (number 1 to 3)    1. my family (go) to the cinema last week ( -, ? )\r\n\r\n2. the student (study) in the laboratory yesterday ( +, - )\r\n\r\n3. she (go) to Bandung two days ago (+, -)\r\n\r\n4. the girl was very happy to hear the good news\r\n ( - ) .......\r\n\r\n5. Active voice : the clever student brings a dictionary in his bag\r\n passive voice :.........\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p> </p><p>1. (-) my family did not go to the cinema last week.</p><p>(?) Did my family go to the cinema last week ?</p><p>2. (+) the student studied in the laboratory yesterday.</p><p>(-) the student did not study in the laboratory yesterday.</p><p>3. (+) she went to Bandung two days ago.</p><p>(-) she did not go to Bandung two days ago.</p><p>4. (-) </p><p>5. Passive voice: a dictionary is brought by student in his bag.</p><p></p><p>cmiiw</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "aniuse-your-carboby-bobyyes-of-course-amy-i-bcould-you-881",
            "question": "Ani:....use your car,boby?    Boby:yes of course\r\n A.my i\r\n B.could you \r\n C.can i have\r\n D.may you",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C. can i have</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu:)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "where-do-edo-and-his-friends-sometimes-gionin-the-afternoon-308",
            "question": "Where do edo and his friends sometimes gionin the afternoon\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>di mana edo dan teman-temannya kadang-kadang pergi di sore hari?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "minta-tolong-yg-bisa-di-bantu-yaa-jangan-lupa-sertakan-cara-n-168",
            "question": "Minta tolong.. yg bisa di bantu yaa.. jangan lupa sertakan cara nya.. terimakasih( \u2579\u25bd\u2579 )\u200b.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>Apa yang mau dibantu?  Soal aja gk ada :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-would-you-mind-not-closing-the-window-the-sentence-has-the-615",
            "question": "6. \"Would you mind not closing the window?\"    The sentence has the same meaning with :\r\nA. Do not close the window, please.\r\nB. Close the window, please,\r\nC. The window must be closed\r\nD. Don't open the window, please.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Do not close the window, please.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "let-me-introduce-you-my-nam-ls-nurfaika-zamrah-im-16-years-616",
            "question": "Let me introduce you my nam ls nurfaika zamrah Im 16 years\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>hi there! nice to know you, have a great day!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>greetings nurfaika</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>hi  </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}